[music]
Hi!  Hello guys, welcome to [music] my
house.  As you can see, we are
very blessed because we moved into
our new house.  And when we moved to the
new house,
Mikey's volcano [music] came into focus.  And this,
we will also have a new blessing.  So, this is all
our baby has been waiting for, all we
need is for us to move.  So,
I'm very, very excited to show you what
we've been working on for half a decade.
He is half a decade old.  Yes.  So almost 5
years [of music] in the making from
building a house to building
from scratch to
catching.  There is no one left.  So this is our
house tour.  Sorry we're late for the
house tour because you know
I only have some things already heated in
my toaster oven.  But now it's possible.  So
welcome to Casa Morada.  Come on.
[music]
So this is our Casa Morada and I am very
very proud of this house because it was
given to us. I'm really tired of
explaining.  I'm out of breath.
[laughter] So anyway this is a
collaboration.  Oh, there's the collaboration between the
Morada and Gonzaga families to give it
to us.  So Mikey's parents gave it to us
and my parents helped us
build this house
.
Guys, in the middle of the video, when
I'm panting, you know
my body isn't used to the heavy
suitcase I'm carrying right now.  So we're a little
tired.  Okay.  So when I get cut
out, we just have beer rolls.
That means Tessy is tired.  Okay.
Who's Tessy?  Me.  I am Miss Tessy Con
Morada.  Maybe my Miss Tessy will be angry
.  Because I'm pregnant.  Okay.  One of my
favorite parts of my house.  This is
our foy.
[music]
Thank you so much, Priselo, for what
I learned from you.  So, I'll turn away
when I mention it because
we also have solar panels attached
to our arm kits because you know
we've been here for a few months now so there are some
shady spots.  In the summer, it
also gets sunburned.  Let's do it so you don't
see it.  If you see it, let's edit it out
.  Or please don't
screen it.  Don't zoom in.   Don't
blur it.  Our interior
designer is Huray Design.  So
we showed it here in our house, which supposedly
has grills.  But of course
we're feeling like Kardashians
because my husband looks like Kanyew.
[music]
So I said no, I want to make a kim k so let's
do it. Mommy
Pinty objected because it looked like a resort but they didn't
know because this is the one that
changes so I just made it
one slab of cement and it's all in one piece and
then we just made stairs that match the color
of our flooring so this is it and then
this is all I decided on,
I'll just put a little design here and then
this is for my curtains.  So there was a time
in my life when I made him what he should be
.  My mom said it's because
she loves [music] more than
electronic music.  So mom said it would be difficult for
us to do [music] no matter
who did it.  It's like there's a
flight every morning for the national
anthem of the Philippines, because that's how it is.
So we just made electronics.  That's
it.  So there and then this one is going
to the basement but I'm not
going to the basement anymore because
I'm tired.  And this one was given to
us by Mikey's mom, I think from
Spain or
there. Today she cleaned it, but
to be honest, the other day
Mikey's golf bag was there.  Here are
his gym clothes.  Here are the
packages.  Now just cleaned.  It was a big
mess [laughter] but now it's fixed.
You are very good.  So there.  Okay.  Next.
This one is our supposedly guest
room for my parents.  When they're here,
of course we'll sing them as we
grow old together.  So they're here so they don't have to
take the stairs anymore.  So what I took here
is a pullout bed.  Then while no one
lives here, not as long as they
sleep here.  So this is what
I'm making into a makeup room.  And then here
[with music] we also put the
cameras.  And then those are the awards.
[music] And as you can see, that's why I can
display it.  When I invited
Bea Boris here, she was very happy and
surprised that I [music] was a
graduate.  'Right?  He didn't know that
I graduated.
He didn't know I graduated.  And Mikey
graduated.  You're smart and I'm [music]
UP, but I'm rich.  Okay.  And then of
course it has a fan.  Open it up,
because the teacher is already sweating a bit
.  I don't really
show this off to everyone, even
at my house in Taytay, at our house in
Taytay, and even at the condo.  I won't
display this either.  But you know, in this house,
I also display our achievements
and even our 10 million.  Although
we won't be taking a close-up because it's a bit
dirty and oxidized, so I fixed it.
So why am I displaying that here in the
house?  It's all because of you guys,
right?  I can see the reason why it was displayed.
It's all because of my netizens.  So of course
I can't not
share it with you because you were with me
when we were doing this and you were with me,
you accompanied me all throughout
my journey.
[sighs]
I'm tired.  So this is our CR, I am
so happy with my mirror because this is
from Hoopo Philippines.  All
my mirrors and all my glass and closures,
they're all from Hupo Philippines.  The
owner of the hoopoe is from Taytay.  So I'm
very proud of our countrymen.  And then
you can change the lighting.
So all my mirrors.  And then this is
from Kanszen home.  Then this is what we have
from Canzen.
So this is where Poly always takes a bath.  Here
he always cries.  This is where
the screaming in the hawk's nest happens because
whenever Poly goes swimming and showers, there's
always something dramatic.  I don't want
a shower.  Here are Poly's scenes.
That's what he is.  And
then for my guest as well.  So that's it.
So many people were surprised by this, they were attracted to it
and opened it.  Of course it's best.  So
our faucet is a bit different
.  Those are all from Kansome.
Thank you very much.  How beautiful.
That look is strange.  And of course free
to hoopo for my makeup.  And then as you
can see here, oh, family.
A family that polarides together visits
the house together.  Because they beat
me.  You know, it's a bit expensive to move in
because my family used to
always live with my sister.  Now it seems like it's always been that way
for me.  So of course I'm responsible for the
electricity, I'm responsible for everything, even the food.
So they are always here.  So anyway
this one is from Miss Den.  This has a smell and
then he has an app that he checks
every few minutes.  So
aesthetic.  Seriously, it's like we're
running a marathon, right?  The one in my breath.
And then this one is our powder room.
[music]
[music] So there, as you can see,
there's M for mine.  Just leave it alone,
sisters.  Not purple.  That's for Morada.
And then this one is ours. You know
that.  I don't need to
explain anymore.  Oh, this one is from Bencab.
Photography by Sir Bencab that
we bought in Baguio when we visited.  And
then you know, it's nice here that
you have wet ones and then there's a
toothbrush.  Or isn't it great?
My wife doesn't know because it's like this above
us.  He also knows that it can be opened.
Why doesn't my husband know?
Mikey has no idea what's going on in this
house.  And then this one,
oh this one.  I bought this in 2018. My
sister and I did something.  My sister and I were dating.
I said I would buy it.  One day I will put it
in my powder room in my own house.
And then finally, this is it.
We now have our own house.  So thank you Lord.  And
then you saw my
hands.  Very social.  Asop.  This
dog is going down.
The smoke is gone.  Let others just retweet.  Asop.
Maybe send it again.  Because I was given
a false impression.  So that's social social
.  So, do you know
my favorite part?
I'm so social that we have a powder room.  Because it used to be that there was only
one toilet for
everyone.  But wow, you'll know
you've relaxed in life when you have a powder
room.  Because you have a room to
powder.  There's a speaker there too.  [laughter]
Yes.  You can see this too.  Yes.
We have a bit of a slab of whatnot here.  Pork
chops.  So that's our powder.  I'm
really really happy with my powder room
because I thought about it too.  I
looked for the tiles.  That's it.  Thank you
powder for being such a good powder.  My
floor.  Okay.  For a time,
powder room became my favorite because I said, "Wow, the
powder room is so beautiful. But for
a time, powder became my problem."  You
know why?  It's noisy.  Then this
flooring of mine that
Juray suggested is not allowed to be wet because
we're giving off La vibes.  So
what happened there?  That thing is getting darker and darker
so it's starting to unravel again.  I'm
just telling stories here as if I were just standing on the
corner.  That
also stressed me out a lot.  We don't need to
re-strip the flooring that was soaked in
this powder.  So for a time
you were a nuisance to me.  But I really really
like my powder room.  Okay, so this
one is my floor.  This is Pergo
Philippines.  You know we made the wrong
decision because supposedly it should just be
higher.  But because we really want
our aim to have hairy bones and
then LA vibes.  So we did it all over the
house.  So when he reads something, it's a bit difficult
.  But you know what's good in Pergo?
Turns out they have other things to
read too.  This is all we chose.  I don't
know why
we chose the one that can't be read.  But their after
service is so nice.  So thank you very much
to Pergo Philippines because every time
something happens here with my flooring,
they're always here and they're always
very accommodating.  That's it.  Okay.  So
this is my room.  My favorite part is also
my favorite part.  [music]
[music]
Yes.  Because we've
been waiting for a house tour for a long time.  Do you know how long
our house tour took because of
this sofa?  Yes.  He was delayed by 5
months because a sofa arrived.   The one
I got from Italy wasn't very good
so I had to return it.  So now
it's here.  This is the Pacifica and this
is all from Patricia Arquola.  Or not?
That's when we feel like we're AD.  This is
from Patricia Arola and from Casabella.
So there I am so so happy.  That's one of
my non-negotiables when
we're doing this house.  It's just being torn down
.  I knew from the start that I would buy
a sofa from Casabella.  I
really like Patricia Arquola.  This is
the Gogan sofa and that is Pacifica.  I
know Patricia Arcola.  You know Miss
Patricia Arcola if you're watching,
comment down below.  F. Patricia Archola always catches me
because Patricia
Arola is the designer.
Miss Karen Davila and
Lizy taught me that furniture [music] is
also in an artist's home.  So if you
want to invest on
good house [music] and good furniture,
invest.  If you want to
make a statement, you can invest in
good furniture.  That's it.  So why is
Patricia Arola catching up with me?  So I know
that Patricia Arola is quite expensive
because her designs are beautiful
and she's quite popular no matter where I
shop.  This is beautiful.  Where is this?  Ah,
designed by Patricia.  Oh, it turns out that
Patricia Ar is really following me.  Everything that
my eyes like is really
his design.  So Patricia if you're packing if
you're watching.  Seriously hacked.
I'm so impressed with the
designs of Miss Patricia
Artiola that I can type them out.
Let's rest first.  Maybe
Patricia Artiola will understand.
[laughter]
Okay.  And then this one,
Cassabella gave me, is a chess set that
I hide every time Poly is here because
the kid plays with it.  Everything is just scratch and
scratch.  He's acting like he's
jackstone or something.  And then this one
gift to me.  And then this one.  All
my flowers are from ginger styling.
Thank you very much, Ginger.  And then as
you can see, of course, we put our
parents here because it's because of
with the help of our parents, they are the
Lord's blessing to us.  That's why we were
able to build this house.  That's them.
Then of course this is our wedding.  Then
I told mommy, "Mommy, I need
to change this because of course when
the baby comes, he needs to be there.
Mommy was angry, why change it? Well,
you can add something like that."  So
he wants to look like he's here,
he's stapled.  So what happens is
I'll just delete them here and then
I'll just put the picture of
my future child.  And then this one is
an olive tree.  This is from Napavalle, but it is still
called Sinal.  We even flew it
because we are from Napa-Vali, [ __ ] from as
California from San Francis.  So it's just like,
sometimes
I like to use olive oil.  So it seems like sometimes it's
not just plastic, it's
And then this
one from Larry's curtain.  They gave
this to me so I could have a little
design.  And then
you do it.
Many people are complaining about why this is
happening.  We're Parry style, aren't we?
From LA Vibes to Parisian style.  They said
you'll regret it, you bastard, but there's
nothing we can do about it.  I've done it
.  It's over.  There's nothing we
can do about it.  So this from Larry's
curtain.  And then of course, are you there?
Yes, okay.  Why do I have a tree here?  It's like
those who
garden among us are building a highway.  Why are
there trees in the middle?  Anyway, okra.
They're planting here in the back.
They turned our side garden into farming.   It's
okay.  Why is the okra cut in the middle
?  At least some lemon juice.
We also have the lime there.  So
anyway, this one is this.  This is no
Gucci either.  I saw this on Ach Liz.
Hey, this is from Japan.  Acari.  Acari
lamps by NoGucci.  The funny thing about this is that
you'll really laugh because he's just a piece of paper
.  So he was delivered.  He's a bit
expensive.  So he was delivered,
he was put in a box.  Mom,
I'm in the states.  Where am I?
Am I in Europe?  It's already done.
Played.  I'll clean everything up.
Thrown away.  The box was thrown away along with what
we had been looking for.  Nothing really.   Luckily,
my supplier is good.  Blank
Studios.  Blank Studios is nice.
He said, "Oh, okay, Miss Alex."
I said because they are gone.
Just take this.  This stand of mine makes me feel bad
that it's
really gone bad.  He said, "No,
okay, we'll just give you 50%. Let's just
split it so
you can have Gucci Lam again."  So that's it, that's what it is
.  Mommy Pinty threw something that was
not funny.
[squeaking]
[music]
You're going to break this.  Here.  Yes.  You know,
I was scared because
the house tour might have to stop later because someone was making a noise.
Okay.  Bost drinks first.
So I'm proud of this painting
because we actually bought it from the
artist himself at his house.  He really
gave it to us.  He even gave a
dedication to Sir Galicano.  I don't
know.  He said, "Mulong and I will meet
."  If I say, "Who is Mulong?"
My art dealer said [laughter], "Miss Alex, that's
Galicano."  Oh no, sorry, I don't
know much.  We are not on a first
name basis and we are not on a nickname basis.
Tell me, sir, how is it?  But if it's
mumbling, then it's Sir Mulong, but
now we're close.  Hello, how are
you?  He himself gave it to me.
I'll insert the picture
we actually took.  I said I'd give you
a good spot in my house.  So
he said okay.  Because he really did
that.  It feels like he's really finished for
me.  So, thank you very much, Mr.  Galician.
But of course, three gives.  This.  This is
our bench.  This is the
casino.  Okay.  This is also from Casino.
These are the sofa, dining room, and
my refrigerator.  Besides, what's mine?  That's what
I said, we're going to spend a lot of money
because that's what
I've been expecting in my head that I want to have
.  So this is the complex that is not a
comp.  Capital bench.  Capital complex
cheer is the name, isn't it, what is this civil
bench for civil civil cases?  If
you wait for the results of civil cases,
you will sit here in civil court.  Many people
inspired this, but the designer is
Pure Janette.  So I really think
we need to get it.  But
of course I didn't get the one
he actually designed because there are more
expensive vintage pieces that
he made himself.  I'm not that
rich.  Okay.  So this one is our TV
room.
[music]
This is our TV room.
My wife always hangs out here.  This is where
Cevy and Kuya Paul hang out while they
play PlayStation.  I hid the
PlayStation because he was out of sight.  But is that
the PlayStation?  This is my finished
cabinet, all my cabinets, cabinet tree,
all my modular cabinets are from Bron
Work.  They are also very good.
The owner is very kind and then
their after-service is also great, if you have a
problem, they will send the staff to come immediately
.  So that's all.  So you can
choose if it's Solihia, if it's American
Style, as long as all my modular cabinets are
all from Bronwork.  So thank
you so much Bronwork for giving me the
best deal and discount.  That's all.
And of course the
prank is still here.
Next to the Bible.  Why did we put it there?
Remember, this is the one who fought against Adam
and Eve.  So we stick to the Bible.
The creation with the enemy.  Okay.
[music]
Our house [sings] is
small
but but but but but but this
[sings] is fast
.  I got the lyrics wrong.  My baby, my
baby.  I hear it on TikTok.  Can't take
my eyes [singing][music]
off you.   You are you
Look at this,
my friends, because if you haven't seen the meet your
garden of Yakua
Pirated [music], I can't use it anymore.   There are
no DVD players anymore, guys.
Especially since PlayStation no longer accepts it
.  So anyway, this one
is a gift from Mom Chi and Dada.
My in-laws gave me their birthday gift.   Is it
beautiful?  White.  So this is from
Kenneth Coponp.  This was their birthday gift to
me last year.  Maybe it's like last
year, you know
we went through a lot.  So that's their gift
to me.  Then, as you can see,
Napoli is already cutting back on pickup
sticks.  I saw Napoli making
pickup sticks for the kids.
I see it in their bag.  I don't
know if this is lacking anything, but it's comfortable to
sit on.  But that's definitely not enough, there should be
more, there are already about 10 missing, that's
five.  Oh my, you'll just have to adjust
to your nephews.  So anyway,
another ucci.  This is what we saved [music]
.  I bought this because it
represented my th
Oh, how many months are you, sis?  Ah,
we are the same.  You're welcome, sis.  Okay, that's what
we have from Antique.
I even ordered it from Antique.  One of
my favorite parts when you enter
the house from here is the first thing you
see are the arches.  Of course there is an arc
here.  Whoops.  You said
our house looks like a church, but you didn't get the
point because I like
arches.  So there's an arc there.  And
then from the front door you will
immediately see this one.  My favorite part
too.  All of them are my favorite parts.
Of course, this is my house.  I designed
that.  This is Court
Kardashian's style.  Oh, did you see
that arch?  That's one of
my favorite things about our house because I saw it
on Cory Kardashian.  When I was watching
Keeping Up with the Kardashians.
I'm just a child.  I've never met
Mikey.  Deep down inside me.  It's beautiful
in a house where your windows are not
rectangles, not squares, but round arcs.
That's it.  And then we aimed because of
this.
My LA vibe is
really nice.  All my arcs,
glasses and doors.  All from glass boxes.
All my windows are arcs there so
you can see how beautiful they are.  Glass Box
Philippines.  You know, when it comes to
quality, you really need to think about
the things that are really important for
you to spend money on.  Personally, because
this is one of the things that is truly
non-negotiable for me with Architect.
Architect Burn, I really wanted to
see only arcs in my house.  So I knew
from the start that I would have to pay for
the windows that would cover the
arc and the glass doors that would be attached
to the arc.  So I chose glass boxes because they are the ones that
can actually eat this slime.
and really good quality.  So
there's a net up there.  Actually, there should be a net for
all of this.  There is a screen.  When I saw it,
I said, "Sorry, sorry, no,
we're losing that problem again."
Tessy girl acted again.  I said it
seems like we can't achieve what
Cordne Kardashian has because it seems like there's nothing.
Lex said it was soft.  It's beautiful.
Please.  It's okay, as long as
we keep the look I want.  So
they removed everything,
reordered, realigned.  They're all from the
states because I know, they're all from
the states.  Then the first time we
opened it, when we opened it,
we were in construction, there were
flies.  Mom just looked at me.  Oh
, there's a fly.
I said, "I'm okay."
If there's a fly, it's part of the house.
I'm a little disappointed because there's no screen
yet.  We have achieved it.  How are you doing
there?  What's going on, [whispering]
Mare?  And then, Alexa, play music
because we have
Mommy Pintiaan's indoor farts.  Do we have
speakers here?  Oh, how beautiful.  Go away,
guys.  I'm just going to get dressed.  Oh, this is
glass too.  You will see me.
'Right?  So now you see there are
speakers there.  We also have indoor
speakers that Mommy Pinty is making fun of.  It was a gift
from Mommy Pinty.  But
I saw that when he was charging, he cut
me off.  He charged.  At first
he said it was my gift to you, son.
You'll have speakers inside and outside so
you'll look really flashy.  Why is it that every end is
cut off?  So Alexa plays music.  What?
Oh, holy forever.  Okay, stop Alexa,
stop music.  Okay.
His soft music fits my dance.  Holy forever.
Because every morning they play
music.  Jen surprised me last night.
The noise here.  I saw, "Alexa, stop
music."  Do they also praise and worship
?  But which is nice.  So that's probably
while they were cleaning.  And then this is
our other arc.  Supposedly there
should be some art here, but
daddy said, "Son, your house will be too crowded."
I said, daddy, that's Kim.  That's Kim
Kardashian.  He said, "
Kim's house is bigger than yours."  Oh.  Is that so
?  Okay.  So, sorry.  Sorry, daddy, if
I was too ambitious.  So this is
my dining
[music]
the Pierre Generet Capital Complex
dining and 12 pieces.  Oh, it's not just 10, it's
10 packs of chairs
.  So there was one time when
I told Mikey that maybe he could sell
his other kidney first so
he could afford it.
[laughter]
Then when we went to the doctor, they
didn't accept us because the creatinine was a bit high
.  Luckily, he was patient and went
down.  Why am I mentioning this?
Court of Kardasia again.
You'll search for that again.  We will search.
I saw it, but it looks like Cor's
vintage one is his.  As for me, it's the same
designer, same company.  So it's
still original.  But do
you see many, many, many chairs like this
that are inspired?  The original of that is
Pure Generet.  So that's it for us.  So why
just this?
I only put arm rests on the two capitals.
Mom wonders if the price of a simple thing is cheaper
than not.  I said, "Mommy, you'll buy
that. Do you want just two chairs? It's
just Mikey and me. You won't have any more
seats. What are you doing? Are
you Euratex monoblocks or what? You don't have arm
rests."  So he said, "Okay,
just order it without the arm rest if it's more
expensive."  So that's the simple reason
.  And then we also dine.  Oh, right
?  It's a trend among Italians.  Because it's Italian
.  Their dining set is low
and there are no glasses.  So it's a good thing
Hopo is beautiful.  They also have
tinted glass that looks like it can
fade.  So, this is from Hopo also
because of course the wood is a waste.  Pretend to
always be readable, always accessible.  So
I put a glass from Hupo on it.  And the
rest is history.   I ca
n't say anything about Casabella's after-sales service
.  Absolutely the best.  At the same
time, there are always Christmas gifts.   No matter
what you buy,
their service doesn't end there.  Right after how to take care of
it, how to clean it, they will really
help you.  And when damaged, they will
really help you.  Sometimes they even have a warranty
.  The people of Casabelas are very kind
.  Okay.  So, as you can see, no,
what you're noticing here in my
house, even in my living room, is that supposedly
we don't have air conditioning here.  But
supposedly there should be a tower here.  Here
there is a tower, here there is a tower.  But
we saw it, we said, hm.  It seems like you won't be able to
do anything else with him.  So
I said, "Mommy, maybe the green one is
centralized."  Gree can do it.
I sold too much.  That's it.  So, all of
our downstairs areas don't have air conditioning, as
you can see, we only have air conditioning vents
on the ceiling.  All of that is from
Gree, the best thing about Gree, the
mommy pinty here is so cold.  Especially when it's getting late
.  It was really a super
comforter while here at the dining room because
the gree was super cold and the
after service of grief was also really good so
when something happened,
they were always there for cleaning, so
thank you very much to gre because
even before our house, we really
trusted gree because when we were renting,
I explained to them that we
used to rent a house when our house was being built
in Taytay, there were air conditioners with our roommates,
we were very cold with all the air conditioners,
but we never had a problem with the
air conditioner in the 2 years we lived there, so
we didn't clean it, but it was
cold because we saw the gree brand,
so we said that gree is good, so
when we approached gree automatic,
I said I like gree because there are others,
I won't say what,
but my sister had a problem, it broke,
so it's really me, even though it's all glass,
guys, when you turn on my gree air conditioner, it's
cold later, it's still all in the back, but
I'm panting because I'm pregnant, not because I sweat, it
looked better
when it was centralized, so if you can afford it,
centralize it  As for
their centralized ones, they are different, as
you can see, I'll show you,
they have different compressor controls, so when
you open this, you won't necessarily
open everything.  You can open it completely centralized
or you can open it only per area
.  So that's the good thing.  So
why are we in air conditioning all day?
Of course
because of one solar.  Thank you for
doing this [laughter] I
have a child,
I said, who are
you? It's so funny,
my husband is hiding
[laughter] it's clean because we vacuumed.
Of course, Shan said
Alex's wealth is in the air conditioner.  We only use the air conditioner
every morning when it's sunny
because of solar.  So my solar is
no other than one solar man.
One solar man is very beautiful.  They have an app
and when they did this automatically
when our solar started, guys, it was
so automatic that half of it was done right away.  Almost 30
to 40% of our electricity has been reduced, especially in
the summer.  That's all
you can do, just pray for it to rain.  But
solar is super, super okay if I were
you.  My sister also is getting solar.  My
mom also got solar because if I
were you, you would have to
invest in solar because
you would get much cheaper electricity.  For me,
that's all.  Okay, now let's go to our
kitchen.  This is my kitchen.
[music]
Mikey will show you the app now.
So that's it or 75 or your profit.  So it seems like
our consumption is almost half of what we're
doing.  So
my electricity bill is almost half off, right?
Turn off the air conditioner.  Why?
Your consumption is 120.  Solar is really beautiful
.  So guys, promise.  One solar
monthly.  Okay.  So this is my kitchen.  As
you can see,
Mommy Pinty and I had another fight here because she kept saying too much,
"What a mess. What a mess you chose."
You should be there for your sister.
Mommy Pinty and I fight a lot because it seems like the
older sister gets mommy's designs
.
My design is really unique.  That which is not new to the eye.
My sister's
design seems to be for millennials or baby boomers.  I'm
like that.  That's an aesthetic feeling
.  So Mommy Pinty doesn't understand,
but this is my choice.  All my
marbles are from Euro Asia.  The good thing
about Euro Asia is that once you order, of course
you order slabs, so if there are any leftovers,
they'll give them to you.  So my
center table in the living room is the slab you left
in my other CR, right?  So
you can still use it.  So that's all
from Euro Asia.  Very beautiful.  We are full slab
.  So as you can see after that
you will see my
beautiful I will clean it first while
we are on the house tour because
I saw something beautiful here in the cabinet
I chose.  They were surprised at how quickly he cleaned up, "Did
I open it?"  And
this one.  Mm.
These are all from Mommy Pinty.  This is in
all fairness to Mommy Pinty,
she gave us her sister's salad master set.
But those La Crus are mine, I bought them
in the state.  Mikey was so angry
because it was so heavy.  My kitchen,
those modular cabinets are from
Scavolini.  I would like to thank
Scavolini because they also gave me a
good discount.  And whenever there's a
problem or something,
their after-sales service is also very fast.
Okay.  Thank you so much Scavolini.  So the
quality of Scavolini is really good
.  My sister also
bought Scavolini when she saw
my kitchen because the quality is so good,
every edge is polished.
That's the beauty of mechanics, look,
pretend you're fighting with your wife, what the hell is
going on,
it's like you're not even fighting [music] because
what are you, you're really going to stop.
Oh no, no problem, because
the mechanic is good.  So it seems like
you and your husband just love each other.  What?  Can't
they hear?  Or pretend
I already have a child.  Eat.  I don't eat
money.  Eat all this fruit.
That's right.  I can act too.  These are
all from Dexterton.  Ah, I didn't buy
this in the states, but this is Dexterton.
They gave me a discount.  This is
from Mikey's cousin.  This is our
hydropure.  So all of my
water, it's soft because it doesn't
leave much of a mark on the steel.
He doesn't mind steel and
mirrors because he's soft.  So
we added salt to it.  So
he's filtered.  But of course
he can't have anything else to
drink, but all my water here is
filtered.  I'm great.
I'm happy with myself, I feel like I've
progressed from Taytay to drinking
canal water now.  But our
refrigerator, of course,
my drinking water is always nature
spraying.  Everyone who visits
me thinks my house is a party,
they always want to have a giveaway.
What's the giveaway?  Nature spray bottle.
They always take nature spray bottles
from me because nature spray is truly one of
the best drinking waters.  You know
why?  Tasteless and clean.  'Right
?  There are flavored waters.  This is
really delicious.  You can
mix it with juice and when
you're really thirsty, it's really delicious.
So that's what we drink from nature spring.
He is still cheap.  Of course, this is the
pantry.  So this supposedly shouldn't be there,
but I put a wreath on it for Christmas
.  Wrath and then what is the
mythic rath?  So I said I couldn't
get rid of him.  I just put it on.
But it's beautiful.  As for me and my
house we will serve the Lord because of
course the Lord Jesus bless us with this
house and our household.  So this is
our pantry where
Poly is always hanging out.  Poly's favorite
here, guys.  What is the patron, is this the reason it was
created?  [laughter] Is this the reason
we became chefes?   We had a
chefes in December because we were doing
live shows.  Why do we have Happy Cup DIY?
Because Poly is very fond of the Happy Cup
scramble.  So we were always scrambling.
Brother Louis gave it to me.  Why?  When
he found out I was on solar,
he was charging his electric
vehicle here, right?  And then of course
this one.  Ah [screams]
fire.  You need to have safety
first.  Fire extinguisher.  In my pantry
of course, Hickary
Orum, Chef Ibes Paraguis, Eyeberry and
Paragis tea will never be missing.  Actually, our house
seems to be becoming a TikTok hub for
people.  Do you have a lawn there?  Do you have any berries
there?  You have a history there.
Usually, our favorite place is here.  So
we're always here.  This is my refrigerator.  This is what
I'm saying that I love so much
because it feels like I can see it.  These people are social
.  Let's see if we can
get groceries.  Hey, I got groceries
and it was clean.  But we will check later.
Maybe some of them have expired.  But it's
in the freezer.  So it's okay.
We're okay.  What are our non-negotiables?   Let's break it down
one by one.  Arc, sofa, refrigerator, and
my red knobs.  Wolf.  That's where I really
invested.  So we really do it, it's
like our budget really doesn't
need to be, mom, I really saved it up
because I was just a kid.  Those are the
things I want to see in my house.  Okay,
next staff quarters.  But this one is our
plate Miss Heart, I'm an evangelist.
I used to go to Heart's house and
she showed me the plate room.   It's
only times 3 in size but longer
.  T's I said, "Oh, I hope
I can have a plate room on my own one day."  And
then now I have that in my playroom.
So I bought this one from ate Marielle.
' Sister Mariel had a garage
sale of plates because Sister Mariel
collects a lot.  So
he sold it.  When I
first saw his story posting,
I saw the picture.  I said, "Ate Mariel,
what is that? I want it made in England
."  He said, "Okay, I'll give you a
discount."  So I bought it from him right away.
And what's nice with sister Mariel?
He said, "I also have a gift for you. A
housewarming gift."  That's it.  He gave
me a plate set too.
Sister Marielle is so sweet.  I said, "Ate Mariel,
you delivered two. That's my gift
too."  As in complete plate set.  That's
it.  Thank you so much, sister Mariel.
Sister Mariel, you are not a blood relative of mine, but you are crying,
but Tony G, who is
my blood relative, has not given anything yet.
I bought this for Christmas.
The sister said that.  So when you watch
this, you tell me you're going to buy it.  You're not
Tony Gonzaga, you didn't become Tony
to defeat ate Mariel.  You're going to
buy me a house warming gift,
I believe you.  And then this is
also my Filipino.  So that's
my playthroom.
How are you guys?  Guys, I'm so drunk.
Seriously.  Doing too much.  Come on.
But I've never gone swimming.
We bought this in Venice from
Mikey.  Mikey was so angry because he
said you should carry it because it's expensive.  That's it
.  We were on our way to the airport when this
[ __ ] happened.  This is crazy.
We didn't even buy it there right
where Mike said it was so cheap
Mikey said go there because
when we went to the factory I was going to buy
it because it was in Venice we had to
buy it there that's just here it's just when
we were coming out of the airport it was
cheaper I just
reacted so let
's just pretend to be my wife of course if
you have any I don't know why
I buy those I also have a lot of
glasses I don't know if
we have the mouth here okay this is all from
antique I bought it from antique
I ordered it 'ba.  We always go
to Antique.  I've been back in
Antique for a while.  So almost everything, including my
coasters, is scattered.  All of that is from
Antique.  The ones I put my trash in,
the ones I put my plants in.
All of that is from antiques.  That hamper is all
antique.
[sighs][sniffs]
Next up is my playthroom.  'Aren't
I so proud of my playroom?  He's only small,
but you know that even though he's small, his
family is complete.  And then
we get together.  How beautiful.  Next is
our laundry.  Wow, that's neat with
the Bible verse.  Be still and know that
I am your God.  Okay, so this is my
laundry.  This is from Bronwalk.  This is just something they're
hiding.  So here
[clears throat] is Sister
Pearley.  He dances with shells.
Pearly shells.  Our laundry and
all.  So here, here they hang out.  That's
it.  And then this one.  That's the
outside.  Then you look here.
[music]
crying [singing]
it will be all my baby is kicking
crying be in my heart
my heartan so that's our drama
in life and then our swimming pool okay
so let's go out for my lanay come with me
I'm getting tired too ah if the
battery is I'm getting tired so this
is our lanay
[music]
This is where my aunt Rquel said she came
from another country.  This is where the
tongue should happen.  [laughter] It's
beautiful, but it's just a joke
.  That's four of them.  So that's where
we used to have a boodle fight when there was
seafood.  So that's where we
hung out while we watched
Poly swim in our swimming
pool.  And then of course this is my
garden.  So everything we have here can be
used outside.  What is that called?
Outdoor furniture.  That's it.  But
we usually take this out when we
eat here because this is where
catering places it.  Oh, this is it.  You see?  This is what
I'm telling you from
Antique Goods.  Nice.  And then this
one also from I'll keep it up to date.  Shopee.
[laughter] On Shopee?  Yes, this is Shopee only.
How beautiful.  I'm Filipino, I don't know if it's from
Bulacan or Pampanga,
I just saw this on Shopee, and then this is
my outdoor stuff.  These
are all Filipino designers so
I took this course in Pampanga.
Albero is from Pampanga and he
built my outdoor things
because Albero and he built
my condo.  I'm also impressed with
their quality.  That's it.  Of course when life gives you
lemons, put it outside.  [laughter] There's
just a fly.  Are we at the market or
what?  So, we have lemons.  Okay,
you're welcome, I'm buying lemons for
display, but we're really going to make lemon juice,
you know, we can squeeze lemons like that
.  That's a shame.
That's not possible.  Besides, I'll actually put it under
your armpits.  It's not possible
as of now.  Oh, how nice the Gree air conditioner is
.  We got in.  So it's also nice
when it's outside, right?  So that's
it.  That's our first floor.  I'll
just go with
PH, it's already 500,000.  Inna, my child.
And my wife is home.
I am very happy.  My heart.  As a
homeowner, when I see
my wife, she is very relaxed.  Because you know
Mikey can survive with just one
sofa or even without a sofa on the carpet
.  But all these
ads we advertise are for beauty products.
He had nothing to do with that.  He has no
knowledge of that.  He doesn't care about
that.  P. So when I see the things
we buy that he doesn't
know anything about, he's just surprised.
He must be one of the payers.  What about him?
'I can see that
I'm relaxing him.  What I feel like
doing is what I am.  Or, [laughter] am
I doing my job as a
wife, which is to beautify
our house and make it homey because that's
our job as homeowners.  You know,
ma'am.  Hey.  Okay, by the way, thank
you so much also to Boys all my paint
from Boysen.  The good thing about
our paint is that we mixed it with my approved
by Huray, approved by my designer.
We really mixed it up because the
outside and the inside are a bit different.
Interior and exterior, exterior,
exterior.
Exterior and interior.  He's a little different
but both white but just different in
some way.  So there's a mix of that.  Before
they produce it, you really have to sign it
because once they mix
it into the purple mixture, there's nothing you can do about
it.  So there thank you so much boys,
the quality of their paint is good.  Okay,
we're going up.  We're going to the beach.
[whispering]
Okay so are you ready?  It's going up,
guys, right?  Okay.  So if you noticed
why the staff was absent, it seems like
our staff is very kind
.  They have nothing, they have nowhere
to go here.  You are wrong.  If
you see here in our communities, there are
small squares.  They are there.
That's it.  There they are.  You're already cooked.
[squeaks] They're
hanging out there.
Of course, we don't want them to be left out
of the house.
We have staff quarters downstairs.
[music]
So they were separated a bit so they had their own
lives there.  But of course
they also have CCTV.  But it's not just about what's
outside, there's still CCTV.  So
our dirty kitchen that I didn't
go to because they said I might get
ligament pain because our kitchen is a bit dirty
right now.  [music]
So of course because they're in the basement,
they also have air conditioning because it seems like there's a
flow of air every time
they sleep.  But their air conditioner is
on a timer.  Just 20 minutes.
Just 20 minutes.  Then the 20 minutes are
scattered throughout the day.
[laughter]
No, they have air conditioning for the drivers
and the staff.  And in one of my rooms, it was
supposed to be my storage room, but
my other editor ran away.  So
I adopted it first.  So to the
Santiago family, I have your son.
He's just here.  He's just hiding.
He's just going through something, but
he'll come back to you in Marikina.
Okay, guys.  Are you ready to go up?  When
I say yes, you say yes.  [whispering] Yeah.
Yes.
You.
When I say go, you say up.  Go.
Go up.
Go up.  Never go down.
But what is Shugodstra?  So maybe
I'll just VO this.  Gonstra is testb.
So let's just wait for the next video, guys.  Have mercy
on me.  I said a lot.
I have explained a lot.  It's been four months since
I've been seen here on the vlog.   I've
done so much today
.  Usually I just lie down and
eat grapes.  I don't usually just
lie down.  So I'm just a little tired
.  But what can we do?
Our next video will be after
I give birth.  It's been a while since
my son turned 18.  Okay.
Our next video, huh?  Is that okay with you
?  Okay.  What to look forward to
next?  Check out.  The feeling.   It's
really fun to visit the
house.  That's why Miss Sharlen
Gonzalez and I are so happy that
you are here today watching at Home Cad.
So this one is our hallway.
Its softness.  That's what I mean by
its softness.  It's like [laughter] a ghost is playing
[music]
in my house.  There is an old man right behind
us.  Streaked.
[music]
Oh, sorry.
No way.   That's what gave
me stress.
[music]